So if we're clear on those basics let's go on to some other basics before we get into some slightly
因此，如果我们清楚这些基础知识，让我们先了解其他一些基础知识，然后再稍微介绍一下
more difficult stuff.
更困难的东西。
Some phrases I want to just make sure you're absolutely clear on these basic prepositions at by around
一些短语我想确保你对这些基本介词绝对清楚 by around
about and within their basic their basic.
关于和在他们的基本他们的基本。
But we need to make sure we're clear on how to use them.
但是我们需要确保我们清楚如何使用它们。
Let's just burn through some examples.
让我们通过一些例子来燃烧。
That means we're going to go really fast.
这意味着我们将走得非常快。
Here we go.
开始了。
That is for exactly when something happens on the clock usually.
那就是通常在时钟上发生某些事情的确切时间。
So at 7:00 at 7:00 p.m. a.m. whatever.
所以在晚上 7:00 到晚上 7:00上午随便。
I have a meeting.
我有一个会议。
OK.
好的。
Pretty simple at 7:00.
7:00 很简单。
Could be another time could be at 7:00.
可能是另一个时间可能是在 7:00。
Seven twenty three whatever.
七点二十三点什么的。
Why would you do something at seven.
你为什么要在七点做某事。
Twenty three.
23。
Anyway at seven I have a meeting.
不管怎样，我七点开会。
OK.
好的。
Please give it to me by Friday.
请在星期五之前给我。
This one's interesting.
这个很有趣。
What does bi mean BI is like before plus on.
bi 是什么意思 BI is like before plus on。
If you say give it to me on Friday it means Thursday Wednesday.
如果你说周五给我，那就意味着周四周三。
These are not OK if you say give it to me before Friday means Friday is not OK anytime before.
如果您说在星期五之前给我，这些都不行，这意味着周五之前的任何时候都不行。
OK.
好的。
Not Friday.
不是星期五。
If you say give it to me by Friday it means Wednesday Thursday Friday.
如果你说在星期五之前给我，这意味着星期三星期四星期五。
They're all OK.
他们都没事。
Including Friday.
包括周五。
So buy is really useful if you say I'll be there by 6:00.
因此，如果您说我会在 6:00 前到达，那么购买真的很有用。
It means no later than 6:00 no later than six.
这意味着不迟于 6:00 不迟于六点。
Could be five thirty could be five 20.
可能是五点三十，也可能是五点二十。
Could be 558 could be six including six.
可能是 558 可能是六，包括六。
OK so if we say then around.
好的，如果我们说周围的话。
If I if I say I'll be there I'll be there around six thirty.
如果我说我会在那里，我会在六点三十分左右到那里。
This is very then mysterious six thirty is like this.
这很神秘六点三十是这样的。
Oh when is it exactly.
哦，具体是什么时候。
Is it six twenty.
是六点二十吗。
Is it six fifteen.
是六点十五吗。
Is it six twenty five.
是六点二十五吗。
Is it six thirty.
是六点三十吗。
Is it six forty.
是六点四十吗。
Yeah all around that.
是的，周围都是。
So around and about are very similar.
所以左右都非常相似。
They're often used in this way to be less clear.
它们经常以这种方式使用，以便不太清楚。
It's not as clear as at.
它不像现在那么清楚。
And it's not as clear as bi because at least by bi we know what the latest time is.
它不像bi那么清楚，因为至少通过bi我们知道最新的时间是什么。
So we can say around when we want to be general when we want to be general and we often use around and
所以当我们想要一般时我们可以说 around when we want to be general 而我们经常使用 around 和
about when we're talking about our memory.
关于我们何时谈论我们的记忆。
For example I could say at at about 5:00 we went out to eat.
例如，我可以说我们在 5:00 左右出去吃饭。
That was maybe yesterday at about 5:00.
那可能是昨天 5:00 左右。
We went out to eat about we could also say we could also use around five as well.
我们出去吃饭，我们也可以说我们也可以使用大约五个。
That's fine.
没关系。
We could say about we could say around.
我们可以说我们可以说周围。
That means that my memory is not so clear.
这意味着我的记忆不是很清楚。
I wasn't checking my watch when we left to go out to eat.
我们出去吃饭的时候我没有看表。
Maybe I and some of my co-workers went out to eat.
也许我和我的一些同事出去吃饭。
When did we go on the food.
我们什么时候去吃的。
I was around.
我在附近。
I was around five maybe about five.
我大约五岁，也许大约五岁。
OK.
好的。
So that's how we use that.
这就是我们使用它的方式。
Either we're going to be late.
要么我们会迟到。
We don't know when we're going to arrive or we don't remember very clearly about around.
我们不知道我们什么时候到达，或者我们不太清楚地记得周围的情况。
OK now what about within here.
好的，现在在这里怎么样。
We have within within 20 minutes everyone was asleep OK.
我们已经在 20 分钟内每个人都睡着了。
So if we say everyone was asleep by 6:00 20 we arrived home at 6:00 and everyone was asleep by a 6 20.
所以如果我们说每个人都在 6:00 20 之前睡着了，我们就到家了6:00，每个人都在 6 点 20 分之前睡着了。
That means the last person to fall asleep maybe fell asleep at 6 19.
这意味着最后一个入睡的人可能在 6 点 19 分入睡。
Anyway six twenty everyone was sleeping OK.
无论如何，六点二十，每个人都睡得很好。
So before or at six 20 but if we say within 20 minutes then we're talking about this duration this period.
因此，在 20 点之前或 6 点之前，但如果我们说在 20 分钟内，那么我们谈论的是这段持续时间。
Do you are 80 I O N.
你是 80 I O N 吗？
All right that more clearly because that's not very clear D.
好吧，更清楚，因为那不是很清楚 D.
You are a t i o n this duration of time is not a time on the clock.
你知道这段时间不是时钟上的时间。
Usually it's often how many minutes how many hours 20 minutes within 20 minutes everyone was asleep.
通常是多少分钟多少小时 20 分钟内 20 分钟每个人都睡着了。
That means maybe the first person fell asleep at 6 0 5 the second person fell asleep at maybe 6 10.
这意味着第一个人可能在 6 点 0 5 分入睡，第二个人可能在 6 点 10 分入睡。
The third person fell asleep at 6 12.
第三个人在 6 点 12 分睡着了。
The fourth person fell asleep at 6 17 and the last person fell asleep at 6 20.
第四个人在 6 点 17 分入睡，最后一个人在 6 点 20 分入睡。
So within 20 minutes so we can use it like that.
所以在 20 分钟内，我们可以这样使用它。
Talk about durations time periods.
谈论持续时间。
I hope it's clear how we use at by around about and within to talk about time.
我希望很清楚我们如何使用 at by around about 和 inside 来谈论时间。
This is pretty easy stuff.
这是很容易的事情。
I know.
我知道。
Just want to make sure it's very very clear in your mind so that you have no doubt when you want to
只是想确保它在您的脑海中非常清晰，以便您在想要的时候毫不怀疑
actually use them.
实际使用它们。